Virginians for Alternatives to the Death Penalty (VADP); Records apap304
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Publications, 1975-2008; 3; 2.6 cubic ft.
  - ABA Journal The Death Penalty, 1987 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 5)
  - A Call for Justice an Assessment of Access to Counsel and Quantity of Representation in Delinquency Proceedings, 2002 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 6)
  - Accountable to No one, 2003 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 7)
  - A Christian Perspective, 1993-1995 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 8)
  - ACLU 2003 Assembly at a Glance (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 9)
  - ACLU 2004 Legislative Project (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 10)
  - ACLU Bill Listings, 2004-2005 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 11)
  - ACLU Fact Sheet, 2004 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 12)
  - ACLU Legislative Alert, 1990 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 13)
  - ACLU Legislative Alert, 1991 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 14)
  - ACLU Legislative Project, 2005 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 15)
  - ACLU Update, 2004 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 16)
  - ACLU of Virginia, 2003 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 17)
  - ACLU of Virginia Report, 2004 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 18)
  - Alaskans Against the Death Penalty, 2005 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 19)
  - "All but Death Can be Adjusted", Undated (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 20)
  - "Arbitrary, Discriminatory, and Cruel", 2002 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 21)
  - The Armband Protest Flyer, Undated (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 22)
  - Before the Virginia General Assembly, 2005 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 23)
  - Brochures, Undated (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 24)
  - CACP Newsletter, 2002; 2004-2006 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 25)
  - California Death Penalty, 2006; Undated (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 26)
  - Campaign for Criminal Justice Reform Newsletter, 2005 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 27)
  - Capital Connections, 2002-2004 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 28)
  - Capital Defense, 2006 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 29)
  - Capital Defense Handbook for Defendants and their Families, Undated (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 30)
  - Capital Losses: The Price of the Death Penalty in NY, 1987 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 31)
  - Capital Punishment, 1994; 1999 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 32)
  - Capital Punishment, 1995 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 33)
  - Capital Punishment 2000, 2001 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 34)
  - Capital Punishment 2001 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 35)
  - Capital Punishment, 2003 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 36)
  - Capital Punishment a Faith Based Study, 2002 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 37)
  - "Capital Punishment for Female Offenders", 1991 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 38)
  - Capital Punishment Global Issues and Prospects, Undated (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 39)
  - Capital Punishment Study Resource, Undated (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 40)
  - Capital Punishment: What the Religious Community Says, 2002 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 41)
  - The Case Against Lethal Injections, 1985 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 42)
  - The Case Against the Death Penalty, 1984 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 43)
  - "The Case Against the Death Penalty", 1992 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 44)
  - The Catholic Opinion on The Death Penalty, 2004 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 45)
  - The Catholic Radical, Undated (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 46)
  - The Chair, 1979 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 47)
  - "Children and the Death Penalty", 2002 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 48)
  - The Christian and Jury Duty, 1986 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 49)
  - Church of the Brethren, 1987 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 50)
  - The Church Speaks: Capital Punishment, Undated (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 51)
  - Civil Liberties Review, 2003 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 52)
  - Common wealth of Virginia Citizen's Handbook, Undated (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 53)
  - Commuted Prisoners, 1998 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 54)
  - Compassion, 2004 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 55)
  - Compassion Newsletter, 2006 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 56)
  - "Constitutional Adjudication and the Death Penalty", 1906 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 57)
  - Corrections in America, 1975 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 58)
  - "The Cost of the Death Penalty", 1983; 1987 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 59)
  - The Crime Victims Report, 2003 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 60)
  - The Criminal Justice Reformer, 2006 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 61)
  - Criminal Justice Research Built in, 1988 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 62)
  - Dead End, 2003 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 63)
  - Deadly Speculation, 2004 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 64)
  - Dead Wrong: an Examination of Prosecutions, 2002 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 65)
  - Death as a Penalty, 1998 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 66)
  - Death as a Penalty, Undated (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 67)
  - The Death Penalty, 1979 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 68)
  - "The Death Penalty", 1984 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 69)
  - The Death Penalty, 1991 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 70)
  - Death Penalty Activism, Undated (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 71)
  - "The Death Penalty and Restorative Justice", Undated (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 72)
  - Death Penalty Developments, 1996 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 73)
  - Death Penalty Essay, 2005 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 74)
  - Death Penalty Fact Sheets, 2004 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 75)
  - Death Penalty Fact Sheet, Undated (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 76)
  - Death Penalty in the USA, 1991 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 77)
  - Death is not Justice, 2001 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 78)
  - The Death Penalty in 2003 Year end Report (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 79)
  - "The Death Penalty in America", 1999 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 80)
  - The Death Penalty in Black and White, 1998 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 81)
  - Death Penalty Information Packet, 1981 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 82)
  - The Death Penalty: The Religious Community Calls for Abolition, 1998 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 83)
  - Death Qualifications as a Biasing Legal Process, 1981 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 84)
  - Death Penalty Reports, 1997 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 85)
  - Death Penalty Report, 2002 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 86)
  - Death Row USA, 2001 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 87)
  - Death Row USA, 2002 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 88)
  - Demand Justice, Undated (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 89)
  - "The Deterrence Hypothesis", Undated (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 90)
  - Dignity Denied, 2002 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 91)
  - Disarming The State's Lethal Weapon, 2002 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 92)
  - Discipleship for Life, Undated (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 93)
  - DNA Tests can Free the Innocent, 2003 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 94)
  - "Does Capital Punishment Deter Crime", 2003 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 95)
  - "Does the Government Waste You Tax Dollars", Undated (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 96)
  - DPIC Fact Sheet, 1983 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 97)
  - DPIC Update, 2005 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 98)
  - "Drug Companies and Their Role in aiding Executions", 2002 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 99)
  - Equal Justice and Fair Play, 2006 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 100)
  - Equal Justice USA, 2006 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 101)
  - Failing the Future, 2000 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 102)
  - Fallibility vs. Penalty Study, 1991 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 1)
  - The Forgotten Population, 2004 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 2)
  - From FSO to Death Penalty Activist, 2003 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 3)
  - "Foreclosed Impartially in Capital Sentencing Jurors and Predispositions to the Death Penalty", 1998 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 4)
  - The Future of the Death Penalty in the U.S., 1994 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 5)
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation, 2005-2006; Undated (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 6)
  - "The Hourglass", 2003 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 7)
  - Human Rights Human Wrongs, 2003 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 8)
  - I Don't Want Another Kid to Die, 2003 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 9)
  - If You Cannot Afford a Lawyer A Report on Georgia's Failed Indigent Defense System, 2003 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 10)
  - Injustice, Guide to the 18th Annual Virgin Film Festival, 2005 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 11)
  - The Innocence Alert, 2004; Undated (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 12)
  - Innocence and The Death Penalty, 1997 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 13)
  - "Innocence and the Death Penalty: Assessing the Danger of Mistaken Executions", 1993 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 14)
  - "Innocence and the Death Penalty: Assessing the Danger of Mistaken Executions", 1999 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 15)
  - International Perspectives on the Death Penalty, 1999 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 16)
  - International Standards on the Death Penalty, 2000 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 17)
  - Introduction to Criminology, 1976 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 18)
  - Israel Law Review, 1991 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 19)
  - Judaism and the Death Penalty Handout, Undated (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 20)
  - Judaism and the Death Penalty, Undated (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 21)
  - "Judges and the Politics of Death", 1995 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 22)
  - "Jurors Views on Due Process and the Death Penalty", 1986 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 23)
  - Justice Quarterly, 1984 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 24)
  - Juvenile Death Penalty Brief, Undated (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 25)
  - "The Juvenile Death Penalty in the US" Draft, Undated (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 26)
  - "The Juvenile Death Penalty Today", 2002 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 27)
  - "The Juvenile Death Penalty Today: Death Sentences and Executions for Juvenile Crimes", 2003-2004 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 28)
  - "Kids Who Kill", 2000 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 29)
  - Killing Justice, 1991 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 30)
  - League of Women Voters, 2004-2007 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 31)
  - Lethal Injection: Why Physicians Should Oppose It, 1988 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 32)
  - Life After Exoneration, Undated (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 33)
  - Lifelines, 2004 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 34)
  - Lifelines, 2007 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 35)
  - Lifetime Without Parole vs. The Death Penalty, 1990 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 36)
  - Mandatory Justice, 2003 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 37)
  - "Mental Retardation and the Death Penalty", 1988 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 38)
  - "Mental Retardation and the Death Penalty", 2004 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 39)
  - "The Methods of Execution Prescribed by S.239 Are Unconstitutional", Undated (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 40)
  - Millions Misspent, 1992 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 41)
  - Ministering to Prisoners, 1984 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 42)
  - Moratorium News, 1999-2000; 2003-2004; Undated (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 43)
  - Moratorium Now, Undated (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 44)
  - Moratorium Now Packet, 1997 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 45)
  - Moratorium Packet, 2005; 2002; Undated (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 46)
  - Moratorium Resolution Draft, Undated (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 47)
  - "Murder is Wrong", 2000 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 48)
  - "Murder is Wrong No Matter Who Carries It Out, Undated (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 49)
  - Murder Victims Families Flyers, 1993-1995 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 50)
  - "The Mystery of Goodness", 1991 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 51)
  - The National Prison Project Journal, 1990 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 52)
  - National Weekend of Faith is Action Guidebook, 2006 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 53)
  - The Next Step Pamphlet, 1999 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 54)
  - National Weekend of Faith Pamphlets, 2004-2005; 2007 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 55)
  - NCADP Conference Program, 2004 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 56)
  - Not in Our Name, 1999 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 57)
  - Not in Our Name, 2003 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 58)
  - NYU Review of Lam and Social Change, 1990-1991 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 59)
  - On The Front Line, 1995 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 60)
  - Open Letter to the President on the Death Penalty, 1994 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 61)
  - Organization of American States, 2003 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 62)
  - The Other Side, 1997 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 63)
  - "The Outrageous Lack of Fairness in Each Stage of Capital Proceedings", 1986 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 64)
  - OUADT Update, 2005 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 65)
  - Position Paper, 2005 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 66)
  - Post Conviction Justice In Capital Cases, 1986 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 67)
  - Post Conviction Relief Mechanisms in Other States, Undated (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 68)
  - Prisoner Reentry What Works, 2007 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 69)
  - Program Report of the VA Coalition on Jails and Prisons, 1992 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 70)
  - Raise the Roof, 2000 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 71)
  - Reasonable Doubts, 2000 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 72)
  - The Religious Community and the Death Penalty, 2000 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 73)
  - "Responding to Murder", 1998 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 74)
  - The Right to Counsel, 2003 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 75)
  - "The Room With no Exit", 1984 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 76)
  - The Snitch System, 2004-2005 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 77)
  - Starving for Justice, 2005 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 78)
  - Statement of Ida Reid, Undated (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 79)
  - Stop it, 1992; Undated (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 80)
  - Sentencing for Life, 1993 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 81)
  - So Long as They Die: Lethal Injections in the US, 2006 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 82)
  - Strategies for Abolishing the Death Penalty, 1999 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 83)
  - Stop Child Executions, 2004 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 84)
  - Stop Executions in Pennsylvania, Undated (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 85)
  - Stop Execution of Mentally Retarded, 1988 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 86)
  - Study Examines Race and Execution, 2004 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 87)
  - TCASK Newsletter, 2005; Undated (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 88)
  - Ten Ways To Fight Hate, Undated (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 89)
  - Tennessee and the New South Organization for Abolition, 2003 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 90)
  - Texas Death Row, 2006 (Box 2 (3-Publications), Folder 91)
  - "Theological Reflections on the Death Penalty", Undated (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 1)
  - "Tinkering with the Machine of Death: The Ultimate Punishment", 2002 (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 2)
  - "Too Young to Die", 2002 (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 3)
  - Toward Abolition of State Killing, 1993 (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 4)
  - Truth in Action Pamphlet, Undated (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 5)
  - Twenty Years of Capital Punishment, 1996 (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 6)
  - "The Ultimate Punishment, a Defense", 1986 (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 7)
  - "Unequal, Unfair, Irreversible", 2000 (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 8)
  - "The United States of America: Indecent and Internationally Illegal", 2002 (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 9)
  - Us Bishop's Statement on Capital Punishment, 1980 (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 10)
  - USA The Death Penalty Briefing, 1986 (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 11)
  - VADP 21 Day Handouts, Undated (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 12)
  - VADP Action, 2003 (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 13)
  - VADP Action, 2005 (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 14)
  - VADP Fliers, Undated (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 15)
  - VADP Leaflets, 2007; Undated (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 16)
  - VADP Newsletter, 2005 (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 17)
  - VADP Statistics, 2001 (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 18)
  - Victim's Families Before, During, and After Trial, 1987 (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 19)
  - Virginia: An Assessment of Access to Counsel and Quality of Representation in Delinquency Proceedings, 2002 (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 20)
  - Virginia Capital Connections, 2007 (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 21)
  - Virginia Capital Connections, 2005 (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 22)
  - Virginia Coalition on Jails and Prisons Report, 1992 (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 23)
  - Virginia Coalition on Jails and Prisons, 1991-1993; Undated (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 24)
  - Virginia Cure Booklet, Undated (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 25)
  - Virginia Methodist Advocate, 2007-2008 (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 26)
  - Virginia State Legislative Guide, 2007 (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 27)
  - The Vision, 2004 (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 28)
  - Voices Focus: Capital Punishment, 1996 (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 29)
  - VOP Mid Year Report, 2006 (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 30)
  - VOP Newsletter, 2005; 2007 (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 31)
  - "What's Wrong With the Death Penalty?", 2001 (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 1)
  - "We Forgive Those Who Trespass Against Us", 2003 (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 2)
  - When the State Kills, 1989 (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 3)
  - Why We Need a Temporary Halt on Executions, 2003 (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 4)
  - Why Would Anyone Want to Get Rid of the Death Penalty?, Undated (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 5)
  - With Justice for Few: The Growing Crisis in Death Penalty Representation, 1995 (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 6)
  - Witness, 1997-1998; 2001-2003 (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 7)
  - Witness for Life, 2004; 2006 (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 8)
  - Year End Report, 2001 (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 9)
  - Year End Report, 2002 (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 10)
  - Year End Report, 2003 (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 11)
- Communication, 1981-2007; 4; 1.2 cubic ft.
  This series is comprised of letters and emails sent to and from members of Virginians for Alternatives to the Death Penalty. A large portion of this series consists of letters to and from various high profile death row inmates in Virginia such as Joe Giarratano and Herbert Bassette.
  - Lethal Injection, 1981; 1988-1989; Undated (Box 1 (4-Communication), Folder 1)
  - Letter to and from Joe Giarratano, 1983; 1988-1989 (Box 1 (4-Communication), Folder 2)
  - Letters from Regan Coleman, 1985-1986 (Box 1 (4-Communication), Folder 3)
  - Letter from Doris "Raven" Darkwin, 1987 (Box 1 (4-Communication), Folder 4)
  - List of Letters Sent to Joe Giarratano, 1988-1989 (Box 1 (4-Communication), Folder 5)
  - Letters Asking for Joe Giarratano's Sentence to be Commuted, 1989-1991; Undated (Box 1 (4-Communication), Folder 6)
  - Henry Heller, 1989; 1993-1994; 1997; 2000; Undated (Box 1 (4-Communication), Folder 7)
  - Letter to and from Joe Giarratano, 1990 (Box 1 (4-Communication), Folder 8)
  - Letter Seeking Commutation of Herbert Bassette's Scheduled Execution, 1991 (Box 1 (4-Communication), Folder 9)
  - Letter from Joe Payne, Death Inmate, 1991-1992 (Box 1 (4-Communication), Folder 10)
  - VADP Letters, 1992 (Box 1 (4-Communication), Folder 11)
  - Disposal of Death Row Bodies, 1993 (Box 1 (4-Communication), Folder 12)
  - Letters to Criminal Justice Policy Group, 1993 (Box 1 (4-Communication), Folder 13)
  - Cost of Housing Inmates, 1994 (Box 1 (4-Communication), Folder 14)
  - Letters to Henry Heller, 1994; 2000 (Box 1 (4-Communication), Folder 15)
  - Letters to and from Joe Giarratano, 1997-1998 (Box 1 (4-Communication), Folder 16)
  - 21 Day Rule, 1997-1999 (Box 1 (4-Communication), Folder 17)
  - 11th Virginia Execution of 1999 (Box 1 (4-Communication), Folder 18)
  - Death Information Center, 1999 (Box 1 (4-Communication), Folder 19)
  - Letters to and from Joe Giarratano, 1999 (Box 1 (4-Communication), Folder 20)
  - Letters to and from Jerry Williams, 1999 (Box 1 (4-Communication), Folder 21)
  - Dr. Kathleen Kenny, 1999-2000 (Box 1 (4-Communication), Folder 22)
  - Governor Gilmore, 2000 (Box 1 (4-Communication), Folder 23)
  - Jewish Community Calls for a Moratorium on the Death Penalty, 2000 (Box 1 (4-Communication), Folder 24)
  - Letters to and from Joe Giarratano, 2000 (Box 1 (4-Communication), Folder 25)
  - Emails, 2000-2001 (Box 1 (4-Communication), Folder 26)
  - Fax, 2001 (Box 1 (4-Communication), Folder 27)
  - Letter to the Mayor, 2001 (Box 1 (4-Communication), Folder 28)
  - Virginia General Assembly Vote Results, 2001 (Box 1 (4-Communication), Folder 29)
  - Letters to and from Herbert Bassette, 2001-2002 (Box 1 (4-Communication), Folder 30)
  - Letters to and from Joe Giarratano, 2001-2002 (Box 1 (4-Communication), Folder 31)
  - Cathedral of the Sacred Heart Calls for a Moratorium on the Death Penalty, 2002 (Box 1 (4-Communication), Folder 32)
  - Church of Arlington Calls for a Moratorium on the Death Penalty, 2002 (Box 1 (4-Communication), Folder 33)
  - Death Penalty Alternative, 2002 (Box 1 (4-Communication), Folder 34)
  - Emails, 2002 (Box 1 (4-Communication), Folder 35)
  - Emails on the Virginia Cure, 2002 (Box 1 (4-Communication), Folder 36)
  - Form Letters, 2002; 2004; 2006; Undated (Box 1 (4-Communication), Folder 37)
  - Advancing Justice Through DNA Technology, 2003 (Box 1 (4-Communication), Folder 38)
  - Capital Defense Handbook Email, 2003 (Box 1 (4-Communication), Folder 39)
  - Colonial High School Lecture, 2003 (Box 1 (4-Communication), Folder 40)
  - Emails, 2003 (Box 1 (4-Communication), Folder 41)
  - Innocence Protection Act, 2003 (Box 1 (4-Communication), Folder 42)
  - Juvenile Justice Group, 2003 (Box 1 (4-Communication), Folder 43)
  - Letters to and from Herbert Bassette, 2003 (Box 1 (4-Communication), Folder 44)
  - Letters to the Crime Commission on the 21 Day Rule, 2003 (Box 1 (4-Communication), Folder 45)
  - Letters to Legislators, 2003 (Box 1 (4-Communication), Folder 46)
  - Missing Prisoner Christmas Package, 2003 (Box 1 (4-Communication), Folder 47)
  - National Lawyers Table Talks, 2003 (Box 1 (4-Communication), Folder 48)
  - Registration for a Weekend of Faith, 2003 (Box 1 (4-Communication), Folder 49)
  - Thank You Letter, 2003 (Box 1 (4-Communication), Folder 50)
  - Virginia General Assembly, 2003 (Box 1 (4-Communication), Folder 51)
  - Virginia Interfaith Center Regional Meeting Invitation, 2003 (Box 1 (4-Communication), Folder 52)
  - VADP Annual Conference Thank You, 2003; Undated (Box 1 (4-Communication), Folder 53)
  - Action Alerts and Media Alerts, 2003-2004; Undated (Box 1 (4-Communication), Folder 54)
  - Murder Victims Families Restitution in Virginia, 2003-2004; Undated (Box 1 (4-Communication), Folder 55)
  - Letters to and from Joe Giarratano, 2003-2005 (Box 1 (4-Communication), Folder 56)
  - 85 Recommendations Project, 2003-2006 (Box 1 (4-Communication), Folder 57)
  - Amicus Brief, 2004 (Box 1 (4-Communication), Folder 58)
  - Amnesty International Chapter Meeting, 2004 (Box 1 (4-Communication), Folder 59)
  - Amnesty International Regional Conference, 2004 (Box 1 (4-Communication), Folder 60)
  - Catholic Diocese of Richmond, 2004 (Box 1 (4-Communication), Folder 61)
  - Charlie King Concert, 2004 (Box 1 (4-Communication), Folder 62)
  - Death Penalty Day, 2004 (Box 1 (4-Communication), Folder 63)
  - Emails, 2004 (Box 1 (4-Communication), Folder 64)
  - Fill the Field, 2004 (Box 1 (4-Communication), Folder 65)
  - Jennifer Rowls, 2004 (Box 1 (4-Communication), Folder 66)
  - Juvenile Death Penalty, 2004 (Box 1 (4-Communication), Folder 67)